<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Sensor Strange</string>
    <string name="title_home">Key Log</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="start">Start Logging</string>
    <string name="stop">Stop Logging</string>
    <string name="message">Click here to start typing.</string>
    <string name="explanation">
        <![CDATA[
        <ul>
        <li>Smartphone sensors\' values <b>can be obtained by any app without permissions</b> in Android which is a threat to privacy.</li>
        <li>This is a vulnerability which can be exploited by a <b>side-channel attack</b>.</li>
        <li>Our Final Year Project aims at establishing <b>a proof-of-concept</b> that an information being typed by a user in a smartphone can be
        illegitimately inferred from the smartphone motion produced while typing.</li>
        <li>Kindly help us by providing sample data. We collect Key presses, Accelerometer and Gyroscope readings while you type in this app. By clicking next, <b>you agree to let us collect Key presses, Accelerometer and Gyroscope readings </b>(Only while you type in this app).</li>
        </ul>
]]>
    </string>
    <string name="instructions">
        <![CDATA[
        <ul>
        <li><b>Turn ON</b> your Mobile Data or WiFi</li>
        <li>Hold your phone in your left hand and tap the keys using your right hand\'s index finger.</li>
        <li>Prefer an erect sitting posture and <b>remain seated throughout the course of typing</b>. Avoid sudden movements.</li>
        <li>Type the sentence as shown on screen <b>including period</b>.</li>
        <li>The characters you type are not shown on the screen, just keep typing. In case of typo, No worries, continue typing from the next character <b>without using backspace</b>. (Make sure you press the period key at end of each sentence).</li>
        <li>You can even type the sentence at a slow pace inorder to correctly type the given sentence</li>
        <li>You will be typing a total of 3 sentences, in which the first and second will be the same.</li>
        <li>After typing the 3 sentences, click <b>Stop logging</b> which will initiate the upload of the files.</li>
        <li>Thanks in advance</li>
        </ul>
]]>
    </string>
</resources>
